IUE-CWA Local 301; Records apap023
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1939-2003; 5; 854
  - IUE Local 301 News, 1967 January 8-1969 September 9 (Box 3 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - IUE Local 301 News, 1969 September 10-1973 December 18 (Box 4 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - IUE Local 301 News, 1974 January 15-1981 December (Box 5 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - IUE Local 301 News, 1982 January-1990 July (Box 6 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - IUE/CWA Newsletter, 2002; 2003 (Box 7 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous strike newspapers, 1954-1971 (Box 8 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - IUE News strike newspapers, 1969-1975 (Box 9 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - IUE News strike newspapers, 1976-1979 (Box 10 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
- Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents, 1959-1985; 6
  Series 6 is composed primarily of job descriptions, summaries, and related documents from the late 1950s to the 1980s. All descriptions are in order of job codes, which are designated in the first few folders of the series.
  - Schenectady Plant Job Evaluation Plan Manual, 1964; revised 1979 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Job Description, Summary Documents, 1950s-1976 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 2)
  - Job Description Code Lists, 1968; Undated (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 3)
  - Job Description Files, Code 0002-0256 (01), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 4)
  - Job Description Files, Code 0501 (01)-0720 (01), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 5)
  - Job Description Files, Code 0911-0969 (01), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 6)
  - Job Description Files, Code 1001 (01)-1238 (08), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 7)
  - Job Description Files, Code 1240-1765, 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 8)
  - Job Description Files, Code 1820-2014 (00), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 9)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2101 (01)-2430 (45), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 10)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2501 (00)-2951 (00), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 11)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3001 (00)-3872, 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 12)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3875-3940 (08), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 13)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3940 (09)-3982 (01), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 14)
  - Job Description Files, Code 4000-4430, 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 15)
  - Job Description Files, Code 4430 (01)-4702 (05), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 16)
  - Job Description Files, Code 5000-5520 (19), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 17)
  - Job Description Files, Code 5701-5920 (01), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 18)
  - Job Description Files, Code 6100-6613 (05), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 19)
  - Job Description Files, Code 7001 (01)-7201 (18), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 20)
  - Job Description Files, Code 7201 (19)-7729 (01), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 21)
  - Job Description Files, Code 8001-8701 (02), 1959-1985 (Box 1 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 22)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 0002 (00)-0601 (05), 1975-1985 (Box 2 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 1)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 0601 (08)-0934 (01), 1975-1985 (Box 2 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 2)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 0935 (01)-1233 (11), 1975-1985 (Box 2 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 3)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 1234 (43)-1782 (01), 1975-1985 (Box 2 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 4)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 1820 (00)-2301 (02), 1975-1985 (Box 2 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 5)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 2301 (04)-2543 (00), 1975-1985 (Box 2 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 6)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 2543 (01)-2951 (00), 1975-1985 (Box 2 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 7)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 3001 (02)-3352 (00), 1975-1985 (Box 3 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 1)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 3401 (02)-3982 (01), 1975-1985 (Box 3 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 2)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 4104 (00)-4702 (03), 1975-1985 (Box 3 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 3)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 5001 (00)-5701 (11), 1975-1985 (Box 3 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 4)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 5701 (12)-6622 (01), 1975-1985 (Box 3 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 5)
  - Job Summary Files, Code 7001 (01)-9095 (05), 1975-1985 (Box 3 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 6)
  - Schenectady Employee Rolls, 1987 (Box 4 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 1-2)
  - Schenectady Employee Rolls, Lists by Job Code, 1988 (Box 4 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 3-5)
  - Schenectady Employee Rolls, 1988 (Box 4 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 6-7)
  - Classification and Job Rates and Upgrades, 1962-1971; Undated (Box 4 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 8)
  - Job Posting and Upgrading, 1975; Undated (Box 4 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 9)
  - Job Description Files, Code 0002 (03)-0664 (05), 1959-1976 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 1)
  - Job Description Files, Code 0664 (06)-0955 (02), 1960-1978 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 2)
  - Job Description Files, Code 0956 (01)-1724 (01), 1960-1980 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 3)
  - Job Description Files, Code 1724 (02)-2004 (05), 1967-1975 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 4)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2004 (06)-2008 (01), 1967-1976 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 5)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2010 (01)-2430 (01), 1967-1977 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 6)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2430 (02)-2501 (21), 1967-1975 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 7)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2501 (23)-2510 (08), 1966-1976 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 8)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2510 (09)-2801 (03), 1967-1976 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 9)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2801 (04)-2938 (02), 1967-1975 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 10)
  - Job Description Files, Code 2949 (00)-3228 (01), 1967-1976 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 11)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3306 (02)-3321 (01), 1967-1976 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 12)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3321 (02)-3940 (02), 1967-1978 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 13)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3940 (03)-3940 (20), 1967-1975 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 14)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3940 (21)-3960 (03), 1967-1979 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 15)
  - Job Description Files, Code 3960 (04)-4401 (03), 1967-1977 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 16)
  - Job Description Files, Code 4401 (05)-4430 (06), 1967-1981 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 17)
  - Job Description Files, Code 4430 (07)-5001 (14), 1967-1977 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 18)
  - Job Description Files, Code 5004 (01)-5701 (01), 1967-1974 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 19)
  - Job Description Files, Code 5701 (02)-5701 (22), 1967-1975 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 20)
  - Job Description Files, Code 5701 (24)-5907 (01), 1967-1981 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 21)
  - Job Description Files, Code 5908 (01)-6222 (01), 1967-1977 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 22)
  - Job Description Files, Code 6506 (01)-7603 (02), 1967-1979 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 23)
  - Job Description Files, Code 7603 (03)-8701 (01), 1965-1973 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 24)
  - Job Description Files, Code 9020 (01)-9095 (05), 1959-1985 (Box 5 (6-Job Descriptions, Summaries and Related Documents), Folder 25)
- Photographs, 1948-1980s; 7
  The photographs in this series generally relate to the work of GE administrator, A.C. Stevens and of various politicians and union gatherings. The collection also includes photographs of IUE Local 301 Pensioners.
  - Bywater, Bill, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Cerebral Palsy Benefit, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Cuomo, Mario, Photographs, 1980s (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Cuomo, Matilda, Photographs, 1982 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - IUE News Political Cartoon Photos, 1980s (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Jennings, Paul, Photographs, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1980s (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Officer Photographs, 1970s (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Pensioners Photographs, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Pensioners, 1977-1980 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Poster board photo collection and associated materials, 1982 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Quirini, Helen, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Stevens, AC, Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Stevens, AC, Project Red Feather, 1959 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Stevens, AC, Photographs, 1951-1967 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Stratton, Sam, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Strike Photographs, 1954-1971; Undated (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Unity Slate Candidates, 1980 (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Thirteenth Annual United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America Convention Photograph, 1948 (Oversized 2)
- Grievance Files, 1959-1999; 8
  Series 8 contains grievance files from 1959-1999. The grievance files represent grievances filed by members of IUE-CWA Local 301 against General Electric for various reasons as well as the recommended actions taken.
  - Grievance Files, 1981; 1982 (Box 1 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1)
  - Grievance Files, 1982 (Box 1 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 2-11)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12)
  - Grievance Files, 1983 (Box 1 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13-16)
  - Grievance Files, 1983; 1984 (Box 1 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 2 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-4)
  - Grievance Files, 1981; 1982 (Box 2 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Grievance Files, 1982 (Box 2 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7-13)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1984 (Box 2 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 3 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-8)
  - Grievance Files, 1981; 1982 (Box 3 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9)
  - Grievance Files, 1982 (Box 3 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10-13)
  - Grievance Files, 1985 (Box 3 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1983 (Box 4 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1983; 1984 (Box 4 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6)
  - Grievance Files, 1984 (Box 4 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7-10)
  - Grievance Files, 1984; 1985 (Box 4 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11)
  - Grievance Files, 1985 (Box 4 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12-14)
  - Grievance Files, 1982 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-8)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1983 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9)
  - Grievance Files, 1983 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10-16)
  - Grievance Files, 1984 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17-25)
  - Grievance Files, 1984; 1985 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 26)
  - Grievance Files, 1985 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 27-34)
  - Grievance Files, 1985; 1986 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 35)
  - Grievance Files, 1986 (Box 5 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 36-39)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1981 (Box 6 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 6 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 2-15)
  - Grievance Files, 1985 (Box 6 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Grievance Files, 1985; 1986 (Box 6 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18)
  - Grievance Files, 1986 (Box 6 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19-22)
  - Grievance Files, 1987 (Box 6 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 23-25)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1987 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1)
  - Grievance Files, 1987 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 2-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1987 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-8)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1989 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1986; 1987 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1986; 1987 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1985; 1986; 1987 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15-28)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1981 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 29)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 7 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 30-32)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 8 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1981 (Box 8 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-14)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 8 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15-20)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1983; 1984 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4)
  - Grievance Files, 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5)
  - Grievance Files, 1983; 1984 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1984; 1985 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7-9)
  - Grievance Files, 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1983; 1984 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12)
  - Grievance Files, 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 9 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13-17)
  - Grievance Files, 1996; 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Grievance Files, 1998; 1999 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 3)
  - Grievance Files, 1994; 1995; 1996 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4)
  - Grievance Files, 1995; 1996 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5)
  - Grievance Files, 1996 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6)
  - Grievance Files, 1994; 1995; 1996 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7)
  - Grievance Files, 1996 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8)
  - Grievance Files, 1976 (Box 10 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9-16)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 11 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-15)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 11 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-23)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 12 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-9)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10-15)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 12 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16-21)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978; 1979 (Box 12 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 22)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 13 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-26)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 14 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-13)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 14 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 14 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976 (Box 14 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16-18)
  - Grievance Files, 1975 (Box 14 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19-22)
  - Grievance Files, 1975 (Box 15 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1979 (Box 15 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6)
  - Grievance Files, 1979 (Box 15 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7-11)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 15 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12-14)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 15 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 15 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16-19)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 16 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-6)
  - Grievance Files, 1975 (Box 16 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7-19)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1977 (Box 16 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 20)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 16 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 21)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 17 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-7)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 18 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-8)
  - Grievance Files, 1976 (Box 18 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9-12)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1980 (Box 18 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 18 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14-25)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11-13)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15-17)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 19 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19-21)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 2-3)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979; 1982 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7-14)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978; 1979 (Box 20 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 3)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979; 1980 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1977; 1978; 1979; 1980 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979; 1980 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8-10)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976; 1979; 1980 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11)
  - Grievance Files, 1979; 1980 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12)
  - Grievance Files, 1968; 1970-1975 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16)
  - Grievance Files, 1974; 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 21 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Grievance Files, 1974; 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4)
  - Grievance Files, 1974; 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1977 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978; 1979 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 22 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15-16)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 23 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-20)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-8)
  - Grievance Files, 1970; 1971 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9)
  - Grievance Files, 1971 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1971; 1972 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Grievance Files, 1971; 1972; 1973; 1974 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1970; 1971; 1972 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1971; 1972 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15)
  - Grievance Files, 1970; 1971; 1972; 1973 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16)
  - Grievance Files, 1972; 1973; 1974 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17)
  - Grievance Files, 1971; 1972; 1973; 1974 (Box 24 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18)
  - Grievance Files, 1968 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1)
  - Grievance Files, 1968; 1970; 1971; 1972 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 2)
  - Grievance Files, 1968; 1972 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 3)
  - Grievance Files, 1973; 1974; 1975 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1977 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Grievance Files, 1976 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1977 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9-19)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 25 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 26 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-9)
  - Grievance Files, 1978; 1979 (Box 26 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1976 (Box 26 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Grievance Files, 1974; 1975; 1976 (Box 26 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1976 (Box 26 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14-18)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1977; 1978; 1982 (Box 26 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 26 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 3)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8-12)
  - Grievance Files, 1976; 1977 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1976 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Grievance Files, 1975; 1976 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16)
  - Grievance Files, 1976 (Box 27 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17-20)
  - Grievance Files, 1967-1969; 1971; 1972; 1974; 1976-1981 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1)